Ready, set...
Doremi Factory!
End stream
Doremi
Factory!
Hi! Good Morning!!
Junbi wa ii kai?
Are you ready?
Kaaten aketara kimi to no Show-taimu
Once the curtains rise, it's Showtime with you
Asobou asobou!
Let's play, let's play!
Waraou waraou!
Let's laugh, let's laugh!
Matteta no watashi-tachi
We've been waiting
Hontou wa kimi no koto o ippai kitai shite
We've actually had a lot of expectations for you
(Inaku naranai de!)
(Don't go away!)
Saisho kara nandatte dekiru wake janai keredo
While it's not like we can do everything right from the start
Genki o shea shite
We'll share our energy
Zettai zettai zettai seichou surunda
And definitely definitely definitely keep growing
Chotto dake no purofiiru
Our profiles are a bit short right now
Itsuka ippai kakitai na
But one day I want to fill them up
Dakara meippai hashaijatte
So is it okay for me to go have a bunch of fun?
Ii no?! Ii no??! Ii no???!
Is it?! Is it??! Is it???!
(Ii yo!!)
(It is!!)
Doremi ga kimi ni asobou asobou
Do-re-mi for you, let's play, let's play
Kirakira na yume egakou egakou
A shining dream, let's draw, let's draw it
Sasotte iru yo kawaii merodii hibikasete
A cute melody is resounding, inviting you
Doremi no you ni odorou odorou
Like do-re-mi let's dance, let's dance
Mune ga hazumu yo takaku takaku
My heart is bursting, higher, higher
Kono suteeji ga daisuki dakara
Because we love this stage
Te o kasanete issho ni tobidasou
Let's join hands and take a leap together
Ima sugu ni
Right now
Asobou asobou!
Let's play, let's play!
Tanoshii tanoshii!
So fun, so fun!
How do you feel now??
Suki ni natta desho?!
You started to like us, right?!
Zutto tsuzuku yo watashi-tachi no Show-taimu
Our Showtime will continue on forever