Okay!Section Chief
President's Decision
An original song for the 3rd Entertainment Division has
Good mornin'!
Cucumber, tomato, and eggs!
And for the dressing...
Hmm, what should I use?
All done!
Perfect.
Ehehe.
Time ta eat!
Time to eat!
Kaoru-chan, do you have lessons today too?
Yup! We're learning this dance that goes like tap, tap, tap!
Kaoru got really good at it!
Be careful not to get hurt by overdoing it.
I'll be okay!
THANKS
Thanks for the meal!
I'm goin' now!
Te to te o tsunaide
Hand in hand together
Kimi to issho ni niji no saki e
Together with you, beyond the rainbow
Takaramono o mitsuke ni
In order to find the treasure
Doa no mukou e dekakeyou
Let's go outside, past the door
Garasu no kutsu mo basha mo nai kedo
Though we don't have glass shoes or a carriage
Jitto shiterarenai
I just can't stay put
Tokimeki no oto takanaru
The beating sound of my heart
kodou no hari chikku takku
The pointer on my pulse goes tick-tock
Mahou no jumon wa kokoro ga shitteru
My heart knows the magic spell
Wakuwaku
So exciting
Hibiku merodii
The resounding melody
Kikoeru?
Can you hear it?
Mimi o sumashite
Listen carefully
Hajimaru!
It's starting!
Minna de "sutaato!"
Everyone's starting together
Hashiri dasou Let's go!!
Start running, let's go!!
Asa da yo ohayou! Asobou!
It's the morning, good morning! Let's play!
Sora ni egaku yume wa
The dream we'll draw in the sky
Taiyou yori mo mabushiku kagayaiteru
Shines brighter than the sun
Genki ni utaou! Odorou!
Cheerfully, let's sing! And dance!
Sekaijuu ni todoke
So that it reaches the whole world
Mirai o terasu hikari ni naru yo watashi-tachi
We'll be the lights that illuminate the future
Te to te o tsunaide
Hand in hand together
Kimi to issho ni niji no saki e
Together with you, beyond the rainbow
Kanaeru yo kiseki sae
As long as there are miracles that can come true
Kirakira ni Shine In The Sky☆
Twinkling Shine In The Sky☆
Episode 9 ~ What has a face that smiles with warmth?
Recently, thanks to their hard work,
Proposal
3rd Entertainment Division
Next Steps
the number of followers for the girls on social media has been increasing, albeit still gradually.
Personally, I would like to take this chance to allow the girls to have a concert,
even if it's a small one, in order for them to gain experience and increase their popularity.
Therefore...
Hmmm...
I don't know about that...
Ah.
Eh?
Yeah, I'm not sure...
Well, I'm aware that they're working hard and all, but, ha...
Even if this project has the president's backing,
when you start scaling things up, problems always start popping up.
Problems, you say?
That's right.
People make such a fuss nowadays,
and if something goes wrong, you guys will be the ones taking the heat.
Right?
Let's just consider them as in-training, for now.
Eh?
Well then, make sure to report to the president about all this.
Alright.
Proposal
3rd Entertainment Division
Next Steps
Oh, uh, but...
Well, there's not much we can do about it.
The situation's just none of our business.
Ahh...
Rawr!
I'm Nina bear now!
Ahh! She's gonna eat me!
Good mornin'!
Good morning!
Producer-san?
Ah, Ryuzaki-san, Ichihara-san, morning.
We're sorry, did we bother you?
It's alright, sorry, sorry.
More importantly, did you need me?
Good luck!
Here I go!
It went in!
New Post
Tag people
Add a description
Share
3rd Entertainment Division Challenge #27
(Nina & Kaoru)
Share
3rd Entertainment Division Challenge #27
Alright, done!
Thanks so much!
Now everyone will be able watch us again, right?
It's hot...
Morning, Tachibana-san.
Good morning.
Arisu-chan!
Morning!
Ah! Hey, hey, Arisu-chan,
could you maybe help me with my homework again today?
Sure, which subject?
Today it's... my picture diary!
Summer Break Picture Diary
Summer Break
Picture Diary
Summer
Break
Picture Diary
Summer Break
Eh?
Arisu-chan?
P-please wait a moment.
I'm looking into it now.
Have you decided what you want to draw yet?
Nope.
That's why I wanted to ask Arisu-chan about it.
Phew... I-I see.
Then how about you draw something you enjoy, Ryuzaki-san?
Maybe something fun that happened recently?
You know, Kaoru really likes cooking!
And also, I like PE, and music, and being an idol!
Oh and then and then, I like jumping rope and omelette-rice!
And then...
Ah, I like flowers too!
Th-that's quite a lot, isn't it?
Yeah!
Ehehe...
Kaoru likes too many things to decide!
have
a live concert!!
"We're small,
but we're idols!"
Based on that concept, composed entirely of children
Then let's try a test drawing.
Yeah, let's do that!
Which should I choose?
Go for it, Kaoru-chan!
Yeah, I'll do my best!
Summer Break Picture Diary
I'll start with crayons!
Okay!
In that case, how about we all go look for something fun together?
Eh?
Hm?
When your head is too full of ideas to decide, you should take a break!
Yay!
Woo!
I'm so excited!
Yay!
City Bus
BUS STOP
Jeez.
What is he thinking, taking us on a trip when we're still trying to get work?
Eheh.
Everyone looks to be enjoying themselves, though.
Koharu-chan, here's some candy.
Thank you~
Hey, it's not safe to be out of your seats!
Okaaay!
What're you looking at?
Our video?
Yeah, it's getting a decent amount of views.
Even my sister's become a fan of all of you!
You two are amazing!
You're so cute! I feel so relaxed watching this!
... a challenge? Good luck!
Congrats~! So cute!
Well done!! Feels great!!
Nina & Kaoru are
great Thx for the cute vid!
You 2 are a-ma-zing!
You're so cute, I feel so relaxed
watching this!
Amazing! Wow
a challenge? Good luck!
Haah!
Hehe, that's great, you two!
Yeah, we got complimented!
Hehehehe...
It's the sea!
Let's race over there!
Ah, hey wait!
Ahhh, wait!
Ahh, hey!
It's a sandy beach!
Wah!
Ah!
Ah, ahhh...
Phew...
Hey, c'mon, you guys are too excited.
So fast...
Haru-chan, you're so cool!
Haru-chan, you're it now!
Run away!
H-hey!
I told you guys, we need to stick together!
Jeez, they're such kids.
Heheh, be careful!
Today's schedule is...
Oh!
DAY 1
Leave
Arrive
Lunchtime
Free time
Sleep
Isn't it lovely?
You guys! Heeey!
We're at the beach today!
It's slightly cold out, so the temperature feels wonderful.
Ehehe...
Ah, it went that way!
Ahhh, kick it!
Haru-chan, kick it!
Kick it, kick it! Come on!
Here it comes!
Yeah!
Hi-yah!
Ah.
Eh?
Wah!
Uh-oh.
Bwah...
Risa-san!
Risa-chan, are you okay?
Haru...
Ah, no, uh, haha...
Excuse me, Haru-san!
That was dangerous!
What if you had injured the lady?
W-what is it?
Momoka, you...
You're not scary at all even when you get angry, huh?
Jeez! Please don't tease me, you all!
Momoka-chan, your cheeks are like sakura mochi!
Nina-san! Jeez!
Mmmmm!
Look, it's amazing!
It's even smaller than Kaoru's finger!
It might be a baby~
It's so small and cute.
Eat a lot and grow big!
Ah?
Wah, it's like the sun!
Everyone, say cheese!
Tachibana-sa...
Arisu-chan!
Look! Look!
Dwah!
You know, there's a bunch of them over there!
Let's go, let's go!
A-a bunch!?
No, I'm fine. I'll stay here.
Hm? Are you not feeling well?
Should Kaoru give you some pats?
It's not that I'm feeling ill...
I'm just... not very good with the summer heat...
You aren't?
I see.
My school teacher told me that we need to be careful when it's hot, too!
It sure is hard when you don't like something, huh?
Kaoru isn't very good with green peppers.
But, you can't play outside then, right?
Tachibana-san, here.
Ah, thank you.
Ryuzaki-san too.
Thanks!
So cooold!
A hat, a towel, some salt candy and...
Ah, did you put on sunscreen?
P-please don't treat me like a child!
I'm not treating you like a chid, I'm treating you like an idol.
Um, I...
Arisu-chan.
Kaoru will try her best to be able to eat green peppers,
so let's try our best together!
Ah...
Arisu-chan, c'mon, this way!
Hurry!
Was it like this?
Please teach me!
For that choreography, you extend your arms slightly...
Ehehe!
Like that!
Ehehe, here we go!
Jump!
Yamajiro
River
Trout
Fishing Spot
Reception Desk
Ameagari niji no machi anata ni ai ni kita  (arere?)
After the rain, I came to see you in this rainbow town (my oh my?)
Doshichatta no? Kurai kao nantoka shite agetai!
What's wrong, you look sad, I want to do something to help you!
Tameiki no CO2 wa (sou da yo)
The CO2 from your sigh (that's right!)
Taiyou abite sumairu kougousei
Bask in the sun and photosynthesize a smile
Waratta anata himawari no hana
Your smile is like a sunflower
Mabushisugi da yo foorinravu!
It's too bright, I'm falling in love!
Dokidoki (Fu Fu) tomaranai (Fu Fu)
My heart (Fu Fu) won't stop pounding (Fu Fu)
Koi o shita fukusayou
That's a side effect of falling in love
Waratta kao ga daisuki dakara
Because I love your smiling face
Kagayaki tsuzuketeitai no
I want to keep on shining
(Shinin') For you
Shinin' for you
(Smilin') For me
Smilin' for you
(Swingin') futari wa
Swingin', the two of us
Zutto zutto issho da yo ne
Will be together forever, right?
Datte datte donna toki mo
After all, no matter what
Himawari wa taiyou to mitsumeaun damon!
Sunflowers and the sun will always gaze at each other!
Nanjuukai demo nanbyakkai demo
Even if it's tens of times, or hundreds of times
Nanzenkai demo nanmankai demo
or thousands of times, or ten thousands of times
Todoketai kono hikari anata no egao no tame ni
I want to deliver this light for the sake of your smile
That was so fun!
Yeah it was.
Man, I'm hungry!
You okay there, Tachibana?
Wah!
We played so much!
We certainly did.
Hm... sniff, sniff!
Something smells really good!
Okay, everyone, let's eat!
Yay!
Nice!
Wow, it looks so good!
Well then, I'll leave it to you, Ryuzaki-sensei!
Ahem! Thanks for havin' me!
It's Kaoru-sensei!
Sensei!
Ehehe, I'm gonna blush.
It's dangerous, so make sure you don't mess around, okay, everyone?
Okaaay!
Kaoru's gonna do her best!
Let's all make a yummy meal together!
First we'll make the dough!
Dry Yeast
Wheat
Flour
Bread flour, pastry flour, sugar, and dry yeast!
100 grams, 100 grams...
Please weigh them!
Whoa!
Why, you!
My bad.
Lukewarm water and olive oil...
And add a pinch of salt!
What should we do next?
Ah, uhh...
Well...
Hm?
Do your best, Producer-san!
You gotta be like a cat!
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meooooow!
Ehh, what should I choose?
There's so much that I can't decide~
This was so fun!
Wow, yours is amazing Haru-chan.
Hehe, looks good, doesn't it?
"To taste"? What does "to taste" mean?
Just write an exact measurement...
Ah!
Ah.
Sugar
Ahh...
A-are you okay?
I guess we can't eat this anymore...
I'm sorry.
Ah...
Are you guys all done?
I'll bake them in turns, okay?
Did something happen?
Leave it to Kaoru!
Kaoru's the teacher today, after all!
Ah...
Do this, and then do this...
Wahh!
Ehh, seriously?
You help too, Arisu-chan!
Okay.
Okay!
Wah!
Can strawberries really go on a pizza?
I wonder how it will taste?
Arisu-chan, here you go!
Thanks for the food...
So, how is it? Did Kaoru do a good job making it tasty?
Ah... Delicious!
Ehehe, that's a relief!
Producer-san.
Hm?
For you!
Really? Thank you.
Thanks for the food!
Mmm!
Well, actually, I really did want to try my best, but I couldn't eat the green peppers...
So I wanted Producer-san to help me...
Ah, but I really did want to thank you too!
Then how about if I do this?
Ryuzaki-san, thank you for making sure everyone had fun today!
Here's a hanamaru as thanks!
Ahh, so cute!
Do you think you can eat the green peppers like this?
Ah, but you don't need to force yourself.
So good!
You're like a teacher, Producer-san!
A-a teacher?
Yeah! You teach us a bunch of stuff about work, and you're always looking after us!
Hey, can I call you "sensei"?
No, I'm a producer.
I'm not someone who's good enough to be called sensei...
Ehh!
No, no, I wanna call you sensei!
Sensei is easier to say!
Hey can't I? Sensei?
Ehh?
Ehehe!
Ah, ahh, wait!
From here on, be sure to teach me even more things, okay?
Okay, I get it!
Sensei!
Today was so much fun, wasn't it~?
I wanna come again!
Yes, it was surprising at first,
but it was a wonderful experience.
You're right.
Honestly, I was anxious about not debuting yet, so this was a nice breather.
I wanna hurry up and meet our fans!
Yeah. Chie wants to work more too.
Section Chief
Incoming Call
Good evening.
It's okay!
Sensei is doing his best, after all!
And also, Kaoru has all of you, and you all have Kaoru, right?
So it'll be okay!
If we ever get down, let's all eat together again!
Yes, it's as you say, Kaoru-san!
Alright, let's keep working hard together!
Yeah!
Section Chief
Speaking
So, I went to report to the president about what we talked about earlier.
And then...
Hm?
Section Chief
I'm sorry, my signal seems to be bad right now...
Hey, can you hear me?
In any case, I've got some big news.
Come light some fireworks with us, Producer!
Ah...
S-sorry, it's a little hard to hear you.
If you could send me an email, I'll be sure to check it later.
Okay, gotcha.
It's time for you good kids to sleep now!
Ehh!
I wanna play more!
You won't grow big if you don't get a bunch of sleep!
That's not very convincing coming from you.
She really got him!
I-I can hear you!
Run away!
Wait!
Ryuzaki-san.
Mmm, what is it?
Um, thank you.
Thanks to you, I feel like I overcame the summer a little bit.
Overcame?
Today was really fun.
Really?
Ehehe, yay...
Haru-chan, let's play soccer again!
Oh, do you like soccer too, Kaoru?
Yeah, soccer is fun!
Everyone, let's start getting back into our seats, okay?
Okaay!
Let's go back.
3rd Entertainment Division
1,076 likes
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me ha
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me ha
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me h
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The firework
so pretty! It's that you all got to go
a summertime trip.
This made me
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
pretty! You made nice memories
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The firework
so pretty! It's that you all got to
a summertime trip.
This ma
Wow! I didn't k
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me hap
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
1,076 likes
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me hap
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me hap
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
3rd Entertainment Division
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happy
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happ
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happ
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me happ
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me hap
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Comments
The fireworks are
so pretty! It's nice that you all got to go on
a summertime trip.
This made me hap
Wow! I didn't know
you could do this with fireworks! Shiny~
You're all so cute!
Thanks for sharing these memories!
Whoa~!! So
pretty! You made nice memories
Fireworks, nice~!!
happy
Hey, hey, Sensei.
We all went glamping together!
Here's a message written
with fireworks!
Kaoru wants to tell your sister thanks for the compliment!
Sure, she'll definitely like that!
We can call her when we get back.
Okay! Kaoru wants to talk to her!
I wanna give back as much as I can to my fans!
That's right.
Let's do that!
For sure, all together!
Yeah!
What's up all of a sudden?
Section Chief
President's Decision
An original song for the 3rd Entertainment Division has
Migi o mite hidari mae muite iku yo
Look to your right, left, then go forward
"Tanoshii koto" sagasou doko ni doko ni aru no? Mitsukedasu yo
Let's search for "fun things", where, where is it? Go find out!
Himawari batake o kakiwakete konnichiwa!
Pushing through the sunflower fields to say hello!
Marude undoukai tokyousou rettsu goo♪
It's like a field day, so let's go race♪
Itsuka kitto shinchou ga nobitara
One day, I'm sure, when I get taller
Miwatashi ryoukou ima yori suteki na sekai miesou
I'll get a good view and see an even more fantastic world than now
Minna de o~kina koe dashite miyou ◎ (nijuumaru)
Let's all let out a great big voice, double-circle
Motto o~kina koe daseta hito himawari no hana○ (maru)
People who shout even louder, a sunflower's flower-circle
Petapetapeta shiiru o hatte kokoro no nikkichou ga
Stamp-stamp-stamp, putting on the stickers
Ohanabatake ni kawatteku yo
will turn your heart's guestbook into a flower field
○ (maru) egaite ○ (maru) egaite hana saite genki no shirushi
Draw a circle, draw a circle, flowers bloom, a lively symbol
Summer Break Picture Diary
Jankenpon paa o dashitara
Rock paper scissors, if you put out paper
Ippai saku yo himawari maaku
Sunflower marks bloom in abundance
Jankenpon pontto tobidase
Rock paper scissors, pop on out
Minna ga iru basho e
To where everyone is
Today we
and everyone
went to the really co
and then in the sea
found a really big
was a fun trip
then everyone
ate pizza
and then